Czechoslovakia Subject Files, Inclusive: 1946-2004, undated, Bulk: 1977-1989
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- General, 1946-2001, undated; 1
  - German Press Articles, 1990 May-July (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - German Press Articles, 1990 August-October (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - German Press Articles, 1990 November-December (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - German Press Articles, 1991 January-April (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - German Press Articles, 1991 May-September (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - German Press Articles, 1991 October-December (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - German Press Articles, 1992 January-March (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - German Press Articles, 1992 April-July (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - German Press Articles, 1992 August-December, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - German Press Articles. Czech Republic, 1993 January-June (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - German Press Articles. Czech Republic, 1993 July-December (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - German Press Articles. Czech Republic, 1994 January-1997 December (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - German Press Articles. Czech Republic, 1998 January-December (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - German Press Articles. Czech Republic, 1999 January-December (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - German Press Articles. Czech Republic, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - German Press Articles. Slovakia, 1993 January-1994 April (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Western Press Articles, 1974, 1982-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Western Press Articles, 1988 January-June (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Western Press Articles, 1988 July-December (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Western Press Articles, 1989 January-May (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Western Press Articles, 1989 June-October (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Western Press Articles, 1989 November (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Western Press Articles, 1989 December (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Western Press Articles, 1990 January-March (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Western Press Articles, 1990 April-July (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Western Press Articles, 1990 August-December (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Western Press Articles, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Western Press Articles, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Western Press Articles. Czech Republic. Slovakia, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Western Press Articles. Czech Republic. Slovakia, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Western Press Articles. Czech Republic. Slovakia, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Western Press Articles. Czech Republic. Slovakia, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Western Press Articles. Czech Republic. Slovakia, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Western Press Articles. Czech Republic. Slovakia, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Western Press Articles. Czech Republic. Slovakia, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Denominational, 1961-2004, undated; 2
  Denominational Czechoslovakia subject files contain categories similar to the general subject files with the focus on a particular denomination and individual prosecution cases of believers and clergy.
  - Adventist Church, 1979-2002 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Individual Adventists: Korinek family (1 of 2), 1984-1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Individual Adventists: Korinek family (2 of 2), 1984-1990 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Baptist Church, 1967-1988, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Baptist Church. European Baptist Press Reports, 1985, 1987, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Evangelical Church of Czech Brethren (ECCB) (Presbyterian) (1 of 3), 1964-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Evangelical Church of Czech Brethren (ECCB) (Presbyterian) (2 of 3), 1968-1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Evangelical Church of Czech Brethren (ECCB) (Presbyterian) (3 of 3), 1968-1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Individual ECCB Members, 1976-1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Individual ECCB Members: Brezina, Ales, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Individual ECCB Members: Komrakova, Bozena, Prof., 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Individual ECCB Members: Litomisky, Jan, 1981-1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Evangelical Church of Czech Brethren Administration, 1977-1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Evangelical Church of Czech Brethren-State-Law, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices Relating to ECCB Religious Activity, 1976-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Evangelical Church of Czech Brethren Life, 1978-1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - ECCB Clergy-Priesthood, 1969-1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - ECCB Clergy: Balaban, Milan, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - ECCB Clergy: Bisek, Tomas, 1977-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - ECCB Clergy: Dus, Jan (1 of 2), 1972-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - ECCB Clergy: Dus, Jan (2 of 2), 1964-1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - ECCB Clergy: Hejdanek, Ladislav (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - ECCB Clergy: Hejdanek, Ladislav (2 of 2), 1977-1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - ECCB Clergy: Kejr, Vaclav, 1976, 1977, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - ECCB Clergy: Keller, Jan, 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - ECCB Clergy: Lojek, Miloslav, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - ECCB Clergy: Rejchrt, Milos, 1971-1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - ECCB Clergy: Simsa, Jan, 1977-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - ECCB Clergy: Trojan, Jakub (1 of 2), 1975-2001 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - ECCB Clergy: Trojan, Jakub (2 of 2), 1968-1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - ECCB Activities Disapproved by the State: Protests, 1977-1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - ECCB Theology-Philosophy-Education-Ethics, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - ECCB Statistics, 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - ECCB Peace Activities, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Evangelical Church, 1971-1987 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Hare Krishna, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Czechoslovak Hussite Church, 1972-1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1955-1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Judaism (1 of 3), 1968-1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Judaism (2 of 3), 1964-2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Judaism (3 of 3), 1968-1973, 1976-1982, 1990, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Lutheran Church, 1959-2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Lutheran Church. Slovak Evangelical Church of Augsburg Confession, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Methodist Church, 1966-1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - New Apostolic Church, 1965, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Old Catholic Church, 1972-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Orthodox Church (1 of 2), 1967-2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Orthodox Church (2 of 2), 1978-1981, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Church, 1973-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Protestant Church, 1961-1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Quakers, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Reformed Church, 1965-1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic/Czech Catholic Church (1 of 4), 1959-1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic/Czech Catholic Church (2 of 4), 1970-1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic/Czech Catholic Church (3 of 4), 1968-1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic/Czech Catholic Church (4 of 4), 1963-1968, 1978, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church/Czech Catholic Church, 1980-1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholics, 1979-1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholics: Adamek Frantisek, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Individual Catholics: Adamek Josef, 1984-1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Individual Catholics: Benda, Vaclav, 1979-1999 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholics: Benda, Vaclav (writings) (1 of5), 1978-1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholics: Benda, Vaclav (writings) (2 of 5), 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholics: Benda, Vaclav (writings) (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholics: Benda, Vaclav (writings) (4 of 5), 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholics: Benda, Vaclav (writings) (5 of 5), 1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholics: Carnogursky, Jan and Carnogursky Pavel, 1980-1991 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholics: Deml, Jakub, 1980-1985 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholics: Fuchs, Jiri, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholics: Janat, Bohumir, 1980, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholics: Kotrla, Iva, 1984-1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholics: Kotrla, Iva (writings) (1 of 3), 1984-1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholics: Kotrla, Iva (writings) (2 of 3), 1970-1985, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholics: Kotrla, Iva (writings) (3 of 3), 1980, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholics: Krizkova, Marie, 1978-1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholics: Maly, Radomir, 1979, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholics: Medek, Ivan, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholics: Micianova, Jana, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholics: Navratil, Augustin (1 of 2), 1985-1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholics: Navratil, Augustin (2 of 2), 1978-1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholics: Neubauer, Zdenek, 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholics: Palous, Radim, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholics: Pavlicek, Jan, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholics: Pospichal, Petr, 1960, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholics: Rompf, Matej, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholics: Rotrekl, Zdenek (1 of 2), 1978-1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholics: Rotrekl, Zdenek (2 of 2), 1943-1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholics: Soukup, Karel, 1977-1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholics: Svacek, Miloslav, 1978-1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholics: Tomek, Jaroslav, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholics: Mrtvy, Michal, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Church Administration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Churches, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Canon Law, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Church Finances, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Bishops' Synod, 1979, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Catholic Dioceses, 1977-1988 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Church-State-Law, 1978-1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Catholic Church-State Relations, 1977-1999 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Catholic Church and Legislation, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Catholic Church and Council for Religious Affairs, 1984-1989 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Reopening (Opening) of (New) Catholic Churches, 1985-1989 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Catholic Church. Commendation in Secular Press, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Oppressive Practices Relating to Catholic Religious Activities, 1980-1989 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Church. Harassment, Surveillance, etc., 1981-1981988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Church. Physical Assault, Murder, 1981-1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Church. Disruption of Meetings-Denial of Rights to Assemble, 1981-1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Church. Fines, 1985-1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Church. Interrogations, 1979-1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Church. Trials, 1979-1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Church. Imprisonment, Arrests (1 of 3), 1978-1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Church. Imprisonment, Arrests (2 of 3), 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Church. Imprisonment, Arrests (3 of 3), 1982-1987 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - State Interference in Catholic Church Affairs, 1967-1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - State Interference in Affairs of Catholic Clergy and Hierarchy, 1981-1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - State Interference in Catholic Church Affairs: Religious & Theological Education, 1981-1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Church. Discrimination in Employment, 1981-1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Church. Trial of Prague Six, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Church. Discrimination in Education, 1982-1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Church. Misuse of Psychiatry, 1983-1989 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Church. Attacks in the Media, 1979-1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Church. House Searches, Confiscations, 1981-1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Church Life, 1975-1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Festivals and Anniversaries, 1979-1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Canonization and Beautification, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Pilgrimages, 1979-1989 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Catholic Church. First Methodius celebration 1985, 1984-1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Parish Life, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Official Catholic Church Publications, 1977-1987 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Catholic Revival, 1968-1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Monasticism (1 of 2), 1975-1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Monasticism (2 of 2), 1985-1998 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Clergy-Priesthood, 1977-1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Hierarchy, 1977-1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Ordination, Election, etc., 1976-1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Clergy, 1975-2000 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Clergy: Barta, Josef, 1979-1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Clergy: Beran, Josef, 1965-1969, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Clergy: Coufal, Premysl, 1981-2004 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Clergy: Dolista, Joseph, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Clergy: Feranec, Josef, 1985-1988 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Catholic Clergy: Formanek, Oskar, 1979-1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Clergy: Gabris, Julius, 1977-1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Clergy: Hlozanka, Radim, 1981-1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Clergy: Jakubec, Josef, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Clergy: Javorsky, Stefan, 1975-1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Clergy: Kordik, Josef, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Clergy: Korec, Jan, 1968-1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Clergy: Labuda, Josef, 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Clergy: Lizna, Frantisek (1 of 4), 1977-1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Clergy: Lizna, Frantisek (2 of 4), 1979-1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Clergy: Lizna, Frantisek (3 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Clergy: Lizna, Frantisek (4 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Clergy: Madr, Oto, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Clergy: Maly, Vaclav, 1980-1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Clergy: Povala, Gabriel, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Clergy: Tkac, Alojz, 1975-1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Clergy: Tomasek, Frantisek (1 of 2), 1977-1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Clergy: Tomasek, Frantisek (2 of 2), 1968-1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Clergy: Trochta, Stepan, Card, 1974-1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Clergy: Trstensky, Victor, 1975-1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Clergy: Zlamal, Vojtech Ales, 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Clergy: Zvernia Josef (1 of 2), 1970-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Clergy: Zvernia Josef (2 of 2), 1984-1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Church. Pacem in Terris (1 of 3), 1967-1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Church. Pacem in Terris (2 of 3), 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Church. Pacem in Terris (3 of 3), 1984-1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Church. Katolcke noviny, 1981-1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Working and Living Conditions of Catholic Clergy, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Clergy-Priesthood Statistics, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Church. International Contacts-Aid-Solidarity, 1976-1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Church. International Contacts: Vatican (1 of 2), 1964-1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Church. International Contacts: Vatican (2 of 2), 1983-1989 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Church. Western Reactions, 1981-1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Church. Visits Abroad, 1984, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Church. Visits from Foreign Delegations, 1982-1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Church. Activities Disapproved by the State, 1978-1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Church. Activities Disapproved by the State: Bratislava Seminary Protests, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Church. Protests (1 of 3), 1976-1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Church. Protests (2 of 3), 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Church. Protests (3 of 3), 1977-1988 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Church. Protests: Eva Greig (1 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Church. Protests: Eva Greig (2 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Church. Protests: Eva Greig (3 of 4), 1981-1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Church. Protests: Eva Greig (4 of 4), 1981-1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Church. Defense of Believers' Rights-Litigation, 1986-1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Church. Conscientious Objection, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Criticism of Catholic Church Policies, 1987-1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Church. Defection-Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Church. Contacts with Foreigners, Émigrés, etc., 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Samizdat Monographs, Anthologies, etc. (1 of 2), 1978-1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Samizdat Monographs, Anthologies, etc. (2 of 2), 1986 and undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Underground Production of Catholic Religious Literature (1 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Underground Production of Catholic Religious Literature (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Underground Production of Catholic Religious Literature (3 of 3), 1981-1989 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Dissent by Catholic Religious Students, 1981-1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Catholic Charitable Activity, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Catholic Church. Oppressive Practices-Persecution-Official Criticism, 1974-1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Theology-Philosophy-Education-Morality, 1977-1987 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Theological Education, 1980-1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Chutrch Statistics, 1977-1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Relations with Fellow Believers, 1977-1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Relations with Other Denominations, 1978-1995 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Religion and National Identity, 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Church Involvement in Secular Affairs, 1976-1989 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Church Peace Activities, 1982-1987 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Literature-Arts-Music-Architecture, 1977-1999 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Women, 1982-1999 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Children and Youth, 1980-1987 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Unity of Brethren, 1979-1988 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Uniate church, 1961-1989 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Samizdat, 3